[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What can you tell me about what we now know about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "what", "we", "now", "know", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, you know, it's a very chilling reminder, Piers, of just how dangerous this whole situation was, especially when this dramatic rescue was carried out by federal agents.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "chilling", "reminder", ",", "Piers", ",", "of", "just", "how", "dangerous", "this", "whole", "situation", "was", ",", "especially", "when", "this", "dramatic", "rescue", "was", "carried", "out", "by", "federal", "agents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "confirm", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Right, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "How is his mother?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "his", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "She is -- right now she's wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "is", "--", "right", "now", "she", "'s", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Do you know how he is?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "he", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "No, I haven't seen him yet.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "seen", "him", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Alabama"]}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "The moment that you heard he was OK, where were you and how soon did you speak to Ethan's mother afterwards?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "that", "you", "heard", "he", "was", "OK", ",", "where", "were", "you", "and", "how", "soon", "did", "you", "speak", "to", "Ethan", "'s", "mother", "afterwards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "UH", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I was actually working and was in Troy, Alabama.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "actually", "working", "and", "was", "in", "Troy", ",", "Alabama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ethan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "So you think he was plotting this all the time?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "think", "he", "was", "plotting", "this", "all", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "What have you been able to do in the last week to try and bring her any kind of comfort?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "been", "able", "to", "do", "in", "the", "last", "week", "to", "try", "and", "bring", "her", "any", "kind", "of", "comfort", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "We have prayed a lot together, we have talked, we have cried together, we've hugged.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "prayed", "a", "lot", "together", ",", "we", "have", "talked", ",", "we", "have", "cried", "together", ",", "we", "'ve", "hugged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "What is your reaction to what happened today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "what", "happened", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I want to start tonight, Piers, by speaking if I can for a moment about the importance of the significance of this date.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "start", "tonight", ",", "Piers", ",", "by", "speaking", "if", "I", "can", "for", "a", "moment", "about", "the", "importance", "of", "the", "significance", "of", "this", "date", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "What is your view about the longevity of Stand Your Ground as a law in America in any state after this case?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "the", "longevity", "of", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "as", "a", "law", "in", "America", "in", "any", "state", "after", "this", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I think that there's two things that come to mind immediately.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "two", "things", "that", "come", "to", "mind", "immediately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Stand Your Ground"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 181, "question": "And I thought, what on earth are these weapons doing in civilian hands?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "thought", ",", "what", "on", "earth", "are", "these", "weapons", "doing", "in", "civilian", "hands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Yes, and that's --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "And what is -- what is your answer?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "--", "what", "is", "your", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Now my question to you again is, if your brother had not gone out with a gun that night, you must surely accept that Trayvon Martin would still be alive?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "my", "question", "to", "you", "again", "is", ",", "if", "your", "brother", "had", "not", "gone", "out", "with", "a", "gun", "that", "night", ",", "you", "must", "surely", "accept", "that", "Trayvon", "Martin", "would", "still", "be", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "You know, there's no telling what would have happened.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "telling", "what", "would", "have", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Were you?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "No, I wasn't there either.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "there", "either", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["two years ago"]}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "EX", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "You know, for me, it was a really interesting situation two years ago being there when the young man used a semiautomatic Glock, but the problem was he used an extended magazine.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "for", "me", ",", "it", "was", "a", "really", "interesting", "situation", "two", "years", "ago", "being", "there", "when", "the", "young", "man", "used", "a", "semiautomatic", "Glock", ",", "but", "the", "problem", "was", "he", "used", "an", "extended", "magazine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"], "LOCATION": ["Arizona"], "PERSON": ["Gabby"]}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Well, who are these people and why won't they wear this?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "who", "are", "these", "people", "and", "why", "wo", "n't", "they", "wear", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "You know, I think one of the things that happened that was really great was seeing Gabby last week at the Senate hearing and saying, we need you to be brave and we need you to be courageous because Americans are counting on you, but the problem has been we have Democrats in places like Arizona who are afraid to touch this issue because they're so petrified that if they come out and say, we want to have responsible and commonsense changes to gun safety laws, that they're going to be hammered back at home as being anti-gun.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "happened", "that", "was", "really", "great", "was", "seeing", "Gabby", "last", "week", "at", "the", "Senate", "hearing", "and", "saying", ",", "we", "need", "you", "to", "be", "brave", "and", "we", "need", "you", "to", "be", "courageous", "because", "Americans", "are", "counting", "on", "you", ",", "but", "the", "problem", "has", "been", "we", "have", "Democrats", "in", "places", "like", "Arizona", "who", "are", "afraid", "to", "touch", "this", "issue", "because", "they", "'re", "so", "petrified", "that", "if", "they", "come", "out", "and", "say", ",", "we", "want", "to", "have", "responsible", "and", "commonsense", "changes", "to", "gun", "safety", "laws", ",", "that", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "hammered", "back", "at", "home", "as", "being", "anti-gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Would you concur with that overview?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "concur", "with", "that", "overview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "What is that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "It's basically -- well, the contract is for the Scientology's clergy, which is called the C-Organization.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "basically", "--", "well", ",", "the", "contract", "is", "for", "the", "Scientology", "'s", "clergy", ",", "which", "is", "called", "the", "C-Organization", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Known as C-Org?", "question_tokens": ["Known", "as", "C-Org", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "This is like the higher executive level of Scientology, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "like", "the", "higher", "executive", "level", "of", "Scientology", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Yes, it's scientology's most dedicated followers.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "scientology", "'s", "most", "dedicated", "followers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "But what is the reality of this?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "is", "the", "reality", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "The reality is that like these pictures, like, you know, these are all rows that we dug, all plants that we planted.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "reality", "is", "that", "like", "these", "pictures", ",", "like", ",", "you", "know", ",", "these", "are", "all", "rows", "that", "we", "dug", ",", "all", "plants", "that", "we", "planted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "How long were you doing this for?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "were", "you", "doing", "this", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "From when I was six until I was 12.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "when", "I", "was", "six", "until", "I", "was", "12", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Would you call it child labor?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "call", "it", "child", "labor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Absolutely, it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturdays"]}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNPS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "How many hours a day would you have to do this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "hours", "a", "day", "would", "you", "have", "to", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "We did the labor for four hours a day every day, except on Saturdays we did it all day.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "did", "the", "labor", "for", "four", "hours", "a", "day", "every", "day", ",", "except", "on", "Saturdays", "we", "did", "it", "all", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "How much of your parents were you allowed to see?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "your", "parents", "were", "you", "allowed", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "We saw our parents once a week.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "saw", "our", "parents", "once", "a", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Did it feel normal because you were around everybody else doing the same thing?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "feel", "normal", "because", "you", "were", "around", "everybody", "else", "doing", "the", "same", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Yeah, I mean, it was normal.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "was", "normal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "How did that feel to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "feel", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well, at the time it was my decision to stay.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "the", "time", "it", "was", "my", "decision", "to", "stay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "In six years?", "question_tokens": ["In", "six", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Did you have much to do with him during this period?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "much", "to", "do", "with", "him", "during", "this", "period", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "ILL: I mean, I definitely saw him throughout.", "answer_tokens": ["ILL", ":", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "definitely", "saw", "him", "throughout", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Is he an evil man?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "an", "evil", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "In terms of how the evilness, if you like, manifested itself, how would you articulate that?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "how", "the", "evilness", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "manifested", "itself", ",", "how", "would", "you", "articulate", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I mean, as a child, you know, of course, the labor that we've already, you know, spoken about.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "as", "a", "child", ",", "you", "know", ",", "of", "course", ",", "the", "labor", "that", "we", "'ve", "already", ",", "you", "know", ",", "spoken", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "That was because he'd gone to China and he'd seen this happening in Chinese schools and liked the idea of it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "was", "because", "he", "'d", "gone", "to", "China", "and", "he", "'d", "seen", "this", "happening", "in", "Chinese", "schools", "and", "liked", "the", "idea", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Right, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Looking back, you must feel completely brainwashed?", "question_tokens": ["Looking", "back", ",", "you", "must", "feel", "completely", "brainwashed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "When I look back, yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "look", "back", ",", "yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Do they let anybody go on the ranch, any outsiders?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "let", "anybody", "go", "on", "the", "ranch", ",", "any", "outsiders", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I think that the church sold the property, so they no longer own it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "the", "church", "sold", "the", "property", ",", "so", "they", "no", "longer", "own", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "-NONE-", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Presumably they have places like this elsewhere?", "question_tokens": ["Presumably", "they", "have", "places", "like", "this", "elsewhere", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Yeah, but the church has a rule that C-Org members can't have children.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "but", "the", "church", "has", "a", "rule", "that", "C-Org", "members", "ca", "n't", "have", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "What is your reaction to people like Tom Cruise when you hear him speak like that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "people", "like", "Tom", "Cruise", "when", "you", "hear", "him", "speak", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "I mean, I think that either he does know what's going on and he's not talking about it or he is willfully ignorant about it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "that", "either", "he", "does", "know", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "and", "he", "'s", "not", "talking", "about", "it", "or", "he", "is", "willfully", "ignorant", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Cruise"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Any child labor?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "child", "labor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Things like that you wouldn't run across there.", "answer_tokens": ["Things", "like", "that", "you", "would", "n't", "run", "across", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Do you think these celebrities are being duped?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "these", "celebrities", "are", "being", "duped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I think that partially.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "partially", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "You have a couple of children, I think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "a", "couple", "of", "children", ",", "I", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Yes, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Have you had any direct feedback from him since you left?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "any", "direct", "feedback", "from", "him", "since", "you", "left", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "No, he hasn't spoken to me since I left.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "has", "n't", "spoken", "to", "me", "since", "I", "left", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "What about any of his immediate family?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "any", "of", "his", "immediate", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "ILL: No, I mean -- well, I mean, my dad -- I mean, not the Scientology ones.", "answer_tokens": ["ILL", ":", "No", ",", "I", "mean", "--", "well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "my", "dad", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "not", "the", "Scientology", "ones", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Do they have any contact with him, with David Miscavige?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "have", "any", "contact", "with", "him", ",", "with", "David", "Miscavige", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Miscavige"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "So basically once you're out of the church, as far as he's concerned, that's it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "basically", "once", "you", "'re", "out", "of", "the", "church", ",", "as", "far", "as", "he", "'s", "concerned", ",", "that", "'s", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What should happen to the Church of Scientology?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "happen", "to", "the", "Church", "of", "Scientology", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "I mean, it should be exposed for the organization that it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "should", "be", "exposed", "for", "the", "organization", "that", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "And to people who are watching this and saying, well, how do we know she's telling the truth, what do you say to them?", "question_tokens": ["And", "to", "people", "who", "are", "watching", "this", "and", "saying", ",", "well", ",", "how", "do", "we", "know", "she", "'s", "telling", "the", "truth", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "CC", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I mean, read my book.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "read", "my", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Has it been hard to repair the relationship with your parents, given that it was almost nonexistent through all those young years?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "been", "hard", "to", "repair", "the", "relationship", "with", "your", "parents", ",", "given", "that", "it", "was", "almost", "nonexistent", "through", "all", "those", "young", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I mean, I've definitely had questions about it and certain things that I didn't understand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "'ve", "definitely", "had", "questions", "about", "it", "and", "certain", "things", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "understand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "What is your view about all the various views put forward about how to make kids safer in schools with the gun debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "all", "the", "various", "views", "put", "forward", "about", "how", "to", "make", "kids", "safer", "in", "schools", "with", "the", "gun", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Well, you're absolutely right, that it is of preeminent importance that we make sure that kids are in a safe and secure environment in our schools.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'re", "absolutely", "right", ",", "that", "it", "is", "of", "preeminent", "importance", "that", "we", "make", "sure", "that", "kids", "are", "in", "a", "safe", "and", "secure", "environment", "in", "our", "schools", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Do you like the idea guns around children generally?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "the", "idea", "guns", "around", "children", "generally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Something has to be done, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Something", "has", "to", "be", "done", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Students First"]}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "ORGAN: What are the overview bullet points you would like to see happen which could radically change America's education system to start making it more competitive?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "are", "the", "overview", "bullet", "points", "you", "would", "like", "to", "see", "happen", "which", "could", "radically", "change", "America", "'s", "education", "system", "to", "start", "making", "it", "more", "competitive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "So there are three primary things that we focus on at Students First.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "there", "are", "three", "primary", "things", "that", "we", "focus", "on", "at", "Students", "First", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "You got to pay them more to get that kind of teacher?", "question_tokens": ["You", "got", "to", "pay", "them", "more", "to", "get", "that", "kind", "of", "teacher", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Well, teachers don't go into the profession because of the money.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "teachers", "do", "n't", "go", "into", "the", "profession", "because", "of", "the", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "But I think too many of them may leave if they feel disincentivised, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "I", "think", "too", "many", "of", "them", "may", "leave", "if", "they", "feel", "disincentivised", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "That is exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Second point?", "question_tokens": ["Second", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Second point is we have to empower parents with information and with choices, so that no family ever is in a situation where they feel like they're trapped in a failing school.", "answer_tokens": ["Second", "point", "is", "we", "have", "to", "empower", "parents", "with", "information", "and", "with", "choices", ",", "so", "that", "no", "family", "ever", "is", "in", "a", "situation", "where", "they", "feel", "like", "they", "'re", "trapped", "in", "a", "failing", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]